<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strongly Branched</title>
    <link>https://stronglybranched.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Strongly Branched</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>stronglybranched@outlook.com (Tony Fortes Ramos)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>stronglybranched@outlook.com (Tony Fortes Ramos)</webMaster>
    <copyright>©2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 21:51:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stronglybranched.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>USB-C device won&#39;t output to a USB-C monitor</title>
      <link>https://stronglybranched.io/2020/01/usb-c-device-wont-output-to-a-usb-c-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 21:51:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>stronglybranched@outlook.com (Tony Fortes Ramos)</author>
      <guid>https://stronglybranched.io/2020/01/usb-c-device-wont-output-to-a-usb-c-monitor/</guid>
      <description>Cable mess ©Alessio CC BY 2.0
   Last holiday I helped my sister find a new setup for her home office. I wanted her setup to be as simple as possible, while still being reasonably priced. The choice fell on the Lenovo 13S-IWL laptop and Dell U2719DC monitor.
Both the monitor and laptop support USB Type-C (USB-C) DisplayPort (DP) Alternate Mode (Alt Mode) which allows for output/input of a DP signal over USB-C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netscaler 11 content switching caching issue</title>
      <link>https://stronglybranched.io/2019/11/netscaler-11-content-switching-caching-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:48:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>stronglybranched@outlook.com (Tony Fortes Ramos)</author>
      <guid>https://stronglybranched.io/2019/11/netscaler-11-content-switching-caching-issue/</guid>
      <description>Flooding at Cache River ©U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service Southeast Region
    TL;DR: Netscalers have an Integrated Cache feature which can cache files even if not licensed. The cache can store corrupted or outdated files. The only way I found to clear the cache in this situation is with an HA failover or a reboot.
 I recently had an interesting issue to troubleshoot: A client was having issues with specifically the Outlook Web Access (OWA) on their Exchange servers, but only when accessed from the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://stronglybranched.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>stronglybranched@outlook.com (Tony Fortes Ramos)</author>
      <guid>https://stronglybranched.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve decided to start writing a technical blog for two reasons. Reason one is the fact that I&#39;ve been immensely helped by all the blogs online. They helped me study for certs, learn new things or just gave solutions to problems at work. I hope this blog is able to contribute back and help others on their journey.
Reason two is more personal. I just want to develop my skills and writing information down is a good way to force myself to really dive deep.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>